<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Innovation Advisory Board &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-type/iab/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 20:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Innovation Advisory Board &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Earl (Duke) Collier</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/earl-duke-collier</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/earl-duke-collier</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Duke Collier served from 2010-2014 as the Chief Executive Officer of 480 Biomedical, a medical device company developing products used in the treatment of peripheral artery disease, and the executive chairman of Arsenal Medical, Inc., a medical device company. Mr. Collier was formerly Executive Vice President at Genzyme Corporation, a biotechnology company acquired by Sanofi&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/earl-duke-collier">Earl (Duke) Collier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Duke Collier served from 2010-2014 as the Chief Executive Officer of 480 Biomedical, a medical device company developing products used in the treatment of peripheral artery disease, and the executive chairman of Arsenal Medical, Inc., a medical device company. Mr. Collier was formerly Executive Vice President at Genzyme Corporation, a biotechnology company acquired by Sanofi for $20.1 billion in 2011. During his tenure at Genzyme, Mr. Collier was responsible for building the biosurgery business and overseeing the company’s efforts in oncology, multiple sclerosis and other immune disorders. He led some of Genzyme’s significant acquisitions and the formation of MG Biotherapeutics, Genzyme’s joint venture with Medtronic Inc., which focused on cardiac cell therapy. Mr. Collier also served as President of Vitas Healthcare, a hospice provider, as a partner at the Washington, DC-based law firm of Hogan and Hartson and as Deputy Administrator of the Health Care Finance Administration (now CMS) in the U.S. Department of Health &#038; Human Services. He is chairman of the board of trustees for the Newton-Wellesley Hospital, serves on the board of Partners HealthCare System and as Chair of the Innovation Advisory Board of Partners HealthCare. From 2006 to 2009, Mr. Collier served as a director of publicly-traded Decode Genetics Inc. (DGI Resolution, Inc.), a biopharmaceutical company, and he currently serves on the board of directors of Tesaro, Inc., a publicly-traded biopharmaceutical company and Transmedics, a private medical device company. Mr. Collier earned a Bachelor of Arts degree at Yale University and received a law degree from the University of Virginia Law School.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/earl-duke-collier">Earl (Duke) Collier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paul LaViolette</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/paul-laviolette</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/paul-laviolette</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Paul LaViolette is Managing Partner &#038; COO at SV Life Sciences. He brings over 34 years of global medical technology management experience. Paul was most recently Chief Operating Officer at Boston Scientific Corporation (BSC), an $8 billion medical device leader. During his 15 years at BSC, he served as COO, Group President Cardiovascular, Group President&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/paul-laviolette">Paul LaViolette</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paul LaViolette is Managing Partner &#038; COO at SV Life Sciences. He brings over 34 years of global medical technology management experience. Paul was most recently Chief Operating Officer at Boston Scientific Corporation (BSC), an $8 billion medical device leader. During his 15 years at BSC, he served as COO, Group President Cardiovascular, Group President Endosurgery, President-Cardiology and President-International as the company grew revenues over 20 times. Paul integrated two dozen acquisitions and led extensive product development, operations and worldwide commercial organizations. He previously held marketing and general management positions at CR Bard, and various marketing roles at Kendall (Covidien).</p>
<p>Paul received his BA in Psychology from Fairfield University and his MBA from Boston College.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/paul-laviolette">Paul LaViolette</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joe Cunningham</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/joe-cunningham</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/joe-cunningham</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joe Cunningham is a Founding Partner and Managing Director of Santé Ventures, an early stage life science and healthcare venture capital company based in Austin and Houston, Texas. Prior to this Joe was a healthcare Venture Partner with Austin Ventures and was previously the Vice Chair of the Ascension Health Ventures investment committee. He is&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/joe-cunningham">Joe Cunningham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joe Cunningham is a Founding Partner and Managing Director of Santé Ventures, an early stage life science and healthcare venture capital company based in Austin and Houston, Texas. Prior to this Joe was a healthcare Venture Partner with Austin Ventures and was previously the Vice Chair of the Ascension Health Ventures investment committee. He is also the former Chief Medical Officer of the Providence Health System and Executive Director of the 300-physician Providence Health Alliance, both of which belong to the Ascension Health system.   He has extensive management experience and is recognized nationally for his expertise in healthcare delivery systems, physician associations and compensation models.  Joe serves on Advisory Boards for both United Healthcare and for Health Services Corporation (BC/BS). He is board certified in both Internal Medicine and Quality Assurance and Peer Review.  Dr. Cunningham received his BS and MD degrees from Texas A&#038;M University and his MBA from Baylor University.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/joe-cunningham">Joe Cunningham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neil Exter</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/neil-exter</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/neil-exter</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Exter currently works at Third Rock Ventures in Boston and plays an integral role in the overall formation, development and business strategy of our portfolio companies. Additionally, he supports the business development efforts within the portfolio companies. He also assumes active leadership roles in the portfolio companies, functioning as interim Chief Operating Officer/Chief Business&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/neil-exter">Neil Exter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Neil Exter currently works at Third Rock Ventures in Boston and plays an integral role in the overall formation, development and business strategy of our portfolio companies. Additionally, he supports the business development efforts within the portfolio companies. He also assumes active leadership roles in the portfolio companies, functioning as interim Chief Operating Officer/Chief Business Officer through the first 12-18 months post launch. Prior to joining Third Rock Ventures, Neil was CBO of Alantos Pharmaceuticals, leading the sale of the company to Amgen. Previously, Neil served as VP for Millennium Pharmaceuticals, directing in-licensing and M&#038;A. Earlier in his career, Neil held various executive management roles within the high technology industry, including tenures at Hewlett Packard and Wang Laboratories.</p>
<p>Neil holds an MBA as a Baker Scholar from Harvard Business School, a MS from Stanford University and a BS from Cornell University. Neil is a member of the Board of Overseers at Children’s Hospital Boston and a member of the Children’s Hospital Boston Board Research Committee. Additionally, Neil is a member of the Partners Innovation Fund at Partners HealthCare and a member of the Advisory Council of the Electrical and Computer Engineering Department at Cornell University.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/neil-exter">Neil Exter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jean-François Formela</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jean-francois-formela</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/jean-francois-formela</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jean-François Formela, MD is a partner at Atlas Venture in the life sciences group and focuses on new advances in biology and drug discovery technologies as well as novel therapeutics. He serves on the boards of Ataxion, Egalet, F-star, IFM Therapeutics, Intellia Therapeutics, Kyn Therapeutics, Navitor, RaNA Therapeutics which he co-founded, Spero Therapeutics and ZappRx. Jean-François&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jean-francois-formela">Jean-François Formela</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jean-François Formela, MD is a partner at Atlas Venture in the life sciences group and focuses on new advances in biology and drug discovery technologies as well as novel therapeutics. He serves on the boards of Ataxion, Egalet, F-star, IFM Therapeutics, Intellia Therapeutics, Kyn Therapeutics, Navitor, RaNA Therapeutics which he co-founded, Spero Therapeutics and ZappRx.</p>
<p>Jean-François has been involved in the formation of companies such as Adnexus (acquired by BMS), ArQule, Annovation Biopharma (acquired by The Medicines Company), Arteaus Therapeutics (acquired by Eli Lilly), Cellzome (acquired by GSK), deCODE (acquired by Amgen), Exelixis, MorphoSys, NxStage, and SGX Pharmaceuticals (acquired by Lilly). He was also an investor in Achillion, CoStim Pharmaceuticals (acquired by Novartis) and Horizon Pharma as well as a board member of Biochem Pharma (acquired by Shire) and Novexel (acquired by AstraZeneca).</p>
<p>Jean-François joined Atlas Venture in 1993 to build the U.S. life sciences franchise. Prior to joining Atlas, Jean-François worked at Schering-Plough, where he directed U.S. Phase IV studies in all therapeutic areas. Before that, he was responsible for the marketing of Intron A, Schering-Plough’s alpha-interferon. He began his career as a medical doctor and practiced emergency medicine at Necker University Hospital in Paris.</p>
<p>Jean-François is a member of the Massachusetts General Hospital Research Advisory Council and a trustee of the Boston Institute of Contemporary Art. He received his MD from Paris University School of Medicine, and his MBA from Columbia University.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jean-francois-formela">Jean-François Formela</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Greeley</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/michael-greeley</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/michael-greeley</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael currently serves as a General Partner at Flare Capital Partners. Prior to joining Flare, Michael served as founding general partner of Flybridge Capital Partners where he led the firm&#8217;s healthcare investments. He also served on the board of International Data Group, the initial flagship Limited Partner for the IDG Ventures global network of funds&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/michael-greeley">Michael Greeley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael currently serves as a General Partner at Flare Capital Partners. Prior to joining Flare, Michael served as founding general partner of Flybridge Capital Partners where he led the firm&#8217;s healthcare investments. He also served on the board of International Data Group, the initial flagship Limited Partner for the IDG Ventures global network of funds and Flybridge Capital Partners. Current and prior board seats include BlueTarp Financial, Explorys, Functional Neuromodulation, Iora Health, MicroCHIPS, Nuvesse, PolyRemedy, Predictive Biosciences, Predilytics, T2 Biosystems, TARIS Biomedical and VidSys.</p>
<p>Previously, Michael focused on emerging-growth company financings with Polaris Venture Partners, was a senior vice president and founding partner of GCC Investments, and held positions at Wasserstein Perella &#038; Co., Morgan Stanley &#038; Co. and Credit Suisse First Boston. Michael currently serves as chairman of the Entrepreneurship Committee of the Massachusetts Information Collaborative and on the Investment Committee for the Partners Innovation Fund and Massachusetts Eye &#038; Ear Infirmary. Michael also serves on the Industry Advisory Board of the Cleveland Clinic, as well as serving on several other boards including the New England Investors’ Committee of Capital Innovation. He was the former chairman of the New England Venture Capital Association and on the Executive Committee of the board of the National Venture Capital Association. Named by the Boston Globe as the “Go-To” investor for life sciences, healthcare and medical devices and a Mass High Tech All-Star, Michael earned a BA from Williams College and an MBA from Harvard Business School.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/michael-greeley">Michael Greeley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adele Gulfo</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adele-gulfo</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/adele-gulfo</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Adele Gulfo serves as Mylan’s Chief Strategy Officer and is a director of Bemis, Inc. (BMS) serving on the company’s Audit Committee. As a member of Mylan’s Executive Leadership Team, she focuses on their key growth drivers, including the company’s expansion into new geographies and the development and growth of its global Specialty pharmaceutical franchise. Previously,&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adele-gulfo">Adele Gulfo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adele Gulfo serves as Mylan’s Chief Strategy Officer and is a director of Bemis, Inc. (BMS) serving on the company’s Audit Committee. As a member of Mylan’s Executive Leadership Team, she focuses on their key growth drivers, including the company’s expansion into new geographies and the development and growth of its global Specialty pharmaceutical franchise. Previously, Gulfo served as president and general manager of Pfizer&#8217;s U.S. Primary Care business unit, which included the Managed Markets and Commercial Operations for all of Pfizer&#8217;s Biopharmaceutical business units. Under her leadership, Pfizer&#8217;s U.S. Primary Care business generated more than $13 billion in revenue. Earlier in her career at Pfizer, Gulfo was instrumental in the development, launch and commercial success of LIPITOR, which became the world&#8217;s best-selling medicine. She was also recognized for her leadership in marketing and medical education campaigns that helped to establish the significance of lowering cholesterol in preventing and managing heart disease.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adele-gulfo">Adele Gulfo</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steve Gullans</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/steve-gullans</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/steve-gullans</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Gullans, PhD, is a Managing Director at Excel Venture Management in Boston. He is an experienced investor, entrepreneur, writer, and scientist. At Excel, he focuses on life science technology companies with a particular interest in disruptive platforms that can impact multiple industries. Steve was a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and Brigham and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/steve-gullans">Steve Gullans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steve Gullans, PhD, is a Managing Director at Excel Venture Management in Boston. He is an experienced investor, entrepreneur, writer, and scientist. At Excel, he focuses on life science technology companies with a particular interest in disruptive platforms that can impact multiple industries. Steve was a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital for nearly 20 years. He has published more than 130 scientific papers touching many areas of biology and medicine, lectured internationally, and co-authored numerous patents. He and Juan Enriquez co-authored <em>Homo evolutis: A Short Tour of Our New Species</em>, which describes the future of human evolution. Steve has spoken at TED and TEDMED on aging, social networks, and medicine. Steve is currently a board director at Tetraphase Pharmaceuticals [TTPH], PathoGenetix, nanoMR, and Cleveland HeartLab, and previously at BioTrove, Biocius, Activate Networks, Catch.com and RxGen, where he was co-founder and CEO.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/steve-gullans">Steve Gullans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Andy Hurd</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/andy-hurd</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/andy-hurd</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Hurd joined Mede Analytics in May 2013 as chief executive officer, bringing with him over 25 years of experience in healthcare IT, including product and market innovation as well as strategic partnerships. Most recently, Andy was CEO of Epocrates (NASDAQ: EPOC),which was purchased by athenahealth (NASDAQ: ATHN). Prior to Epocrates, Andyserved as chairman and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/andy-hurd">Andy Hurd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Hurd joined Mede Analytics in May 2013 as chief executive officer, bringing with him over 25 years of experience in healthcare IT, including product and market innovation as well as strategic partnerships.</p>
<p>Most recently, Andy was CEO of Epocrates (NASDAQ: EPOC),which was purchased by athenahealth (NASDAQ: ATHN). Prior to Epocrates, Andyserved as chairman and CEO of Carefx, which was acquired by Harris Corporation (NYSE: HRS) in 2011. During his six-year tenure at Carefx, the company achievedstrong growth in revenue, income and shareholder value. Before Carefx, Hurdheld senior management positions at WebMD, LLC (NASDAQ: WBMD) and QuadraMed Corporation.</p>
<p>Andy holds a bachelor&#8217;s degree in business administration from Northern Arizona University, and he is a member of the board of directors of Ability Networks and the Cleveland Clinic Innovations Advisory Board.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/andy-hurd">Andy Hurd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ed Kania</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ed-kania</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/ed-kania</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ed Kania is Managing Partner and Chairman of Flagship Ventures, a firm he co-founded in 2000. Ed has 29 years of experience in the venture capital industry and has been involved in the founding, financing, and development of dozens of life science technology companies including several that have emerged as major independent enterprises or significant&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ed-kania">Ed Kania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ed Kania is Managing Partner and Chairman of Flagship Ventures, a firm he co-founded in 2000. Ed has 29 years of experience in the venture capital industry and has been involved in the founding, financing, and development of dozens of life science technology companies including several that have emerged as major independent enterprises or significant acquisitions. Mr. Kania currently serves as a director of several privately held companies. He earned his undergraduate degree in physics from Dartmouth College and his MBA from Harvard Business School.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ed-kania">Ed Kania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
