<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 19:24:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/sri-ramachandra-medicalcentre</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 19:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Case Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/case-studies/max-india-group-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chennai, India Partners Medical International (PMI) and Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre developed an intensive collaboration to improve quality according to international standards. The Challenge Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre opened in 1985 as the tertiary care, multi-specialty teaching hospital of a new public medical college. After years of working with PMI on reforming the school’s education&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/sri-ramachandra-medicalcentre">Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Chennai, India</h2>
<p>Partners Medical International (PMI) and Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre developed an intensive collaboration to improve quality according to international standards.</p>
<h3>The Challenge</h3>
<p>Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre opened in 1985 as the tertiary care, multi-specialty teaching hospital of a new public medical college. After years of working with PMI on reforming the school’s education programs, Sri Ramachandra asked us for assistance achieving the following objectives:</p>
<ul>
<li>Design a quality management system for the hospital</li>
<li>Institute a culture of continuous quality improvement that empowered and staff to play active roles in managing quality</li>
<li>Enhance quality in specific areas of service</li>
<li>Meet the requirements for accreditation by Joint Commission International (JCI)</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Delivered</h3>
<ul>
<li>Advice on how to structure an effective quality improvement journey, including the teams, structures, and processes required</li>
<li>Education and training to familiarize the Sri Ramachandra team with the JCI standards</li>
<li>Critical inputs for specific task forces and committees assigned to carry out quality improvement initiatives</li>
<li>Ongoing on-site and teleconference-based training on specific quality topics, with an emphasis on areas of difficulty</li>
<li>On-site mock quality assessments &#8212; mirroring the JCI survey process</li>
</ul>
<h3>Our Impact</h3>
<ul>
<li>Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre was accredited by JCl on its first attempt</li>
<li>Leadership and staff at the hospital have the capacity to build on the quality improvement journey and maintain high quality</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/sri-ramachandra-medicalcentre">Sri Ramachandra Medical Centre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Max India Group</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/max-india-group</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 16:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Case Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/case-studies/global-experience-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Delhi, India Max India Group has undertaken an innovative and transformative plan to build a premier integrated health sciences institute in northern India. This institute will bring together world-class clinical care, higher education, and research for the first time in India. The Challenge Max India Group is an established private sector enterprise with an excellent&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/max-india-group">Max India Group</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Delhi, India</h2>
<p>Max India Group has undertaken an innovative and transformative plan to build a premier integrated health sciences institute in northern India. This institute will bring together world-class clinical care, higher education, and research for the first time in India.</p>
<h3>The Challenge</h3>
<p>Max India Group is an established private sector enterprise with an excellent service record in them health care and insurance domains. Max has an ambitious plan to become a leading provider of health sciences education. The envisioned Max university includes the following components:</p>
<ul>
<li>College of Medicine</li>
<li>College of Nursing, Allied Health and Wellness</li>
<li>Center for basic and advanced research</li>
<li>Affiliated teaching hospital</li>
<li>Other facilities, programs, and amenities to support a new kind of Indian education campus</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Delivered</h3>
<ul>
<li>Project management: Managing a multidisciplinary project involving teams from multiple organizations, including academic institutions and providers of professional services</li>
<li>Strategic planning: Leading efforts to define and refine the vision, mission, and long-term, broad goals and objectives for the medical, nursing , and allied health colleges that will comprise the institute</li>
<li>Governance: Assisting with the development of optimal governance and organizational structures to guide the operational planning and leadership of the institute</li>
<li>Curriculum planning: Assisting with the development of an innovative curriculum plan based on an interprofessional learning philosophy that integrates educational experiences across the medicine, nursing, and allied health domains</li>
<li>Academic program planning: Providing inputs into the development of faculty development, student life, and program evaluation</li>
<li>Facilities planning: Advising on the development of an overall approach to facilities and campus planning that supports the delivery of high-quality health education and promotes the integration of the education effort with Max’s clinical and societal mission</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/max-india-group">Max India Group</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Experience</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/global-experience</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Case Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/case-studies/wockhardt-hospitals-limited-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>India Partners Medical International (PMI) has the experience and expertise to assist institutions in India that are at the forefront of this country’s health care transformation. Essential Expertise for India’s Unique Challenges Strategic planning to define and refine positioning in an increasingly competitive markets Clinical program and facilities planning to support cost-effectiveness and flexibility and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/global-experience">Global Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>India</h2>
<p>Partners Medical International (PMI) has the experience and expertise to assist institutions in India that are at the forefront of this country’s health care transformation.</p>
<h3>Essential Expertise for India’s Unique Challenges</h3>
<ul>
<li>Strategic planning to define and refine positioning in an increasingly competitive markets</li>
<li>Clinical program and facilities planning to support cost-effectiveness and flexibility and meet growing demand for high-quality specialty care</li>
<li>Quality improvement programs to enhance patient and staff satisfaction and meet international standards for accreditation</li>
<li>Strategies to attract, recruit, and retain top health care professionals</li>
<li>Leadership development and health care management training programs for physician-executives and hospital management</li>
<li>Clinical mentoring and remote consultation to support physician management of complex medical cases</li>
<li>Education and training for physicians, nurses, and allied health professionals as well as administrators to support efficient delivery of quality care</li>
</ul>
<h3>Notable Achievements</h3>
<ul>
<li>Advised on a national growth and development strategy for a new hospital system, enabling it to become a major player in the emerging private health care sector</li>
<li>Guided three hospitals through intensive quality improvement programs resulting in international accreditation, including the first public teaching hospital in India to receive the distinction</li>
<li>Developed a nationally acclaimed nursing leadership certification program replicable across an entire regional network</li>
<li>Provided quality assessment, benchmarking, and clinical mentoring to advance the development of numerous clinical service lines and departments, including oncology, emergency medicine, critical care, and plastic surgery</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/global-experience">Global Experience</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wockhardt Hospitals Limited</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/wockhardt-hospitals-limited</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Case Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/?p=2388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mumbai, India Wockhardt Hospitals and Partners Medical International (PMI) have worked together for a decade on initiatives designed to make their hospital network a high-performing organization offering international-standard clinical services in a challenging and competitive environment The Challenge Wockhardt is emblematic of the new wave of high-tech corporate health care networks in India. To succeed&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/wockhardt-hospitals-limited">Wockhardt Hospitals Limited</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Mumbai, India</h2>
<p>Wockhardt Hospitals and Partners Medical International (PMI) have worked together for a decade on initiatives designed to make their hospital network a high-performing organization offering international-standard clinical services in a challenging and competitive environment</p>
<h3>The Challenge</h3>
<p>Wockhardt is emblematic of the new wave of high-tech corporate health care networks in India. To succeed in India’s increasingly competitive health care market, and position itself as a leading international health care provider for foreign patients, Wockhardt desired to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Develop the overall strategic plan for its national chain</li>
<li>Enhance its clinical programs using international bench marks of quality and effectiveness</li>
<li>Determine the appropriate mix of clinical programs for its member hospitals</li>
<li>Build the capacity of health care professionals and hospital leaders in their respective areas of focus and responsibility</li>
</ul>
<h3>What We Delivered</h3>
<ul>
<li>Critical inputs on the Wockhardt overall strategic plan for new development of clinical programs and facilities and positioning in the marketplace</li>
<li>Co-development of an intensive multi-year quality management and performance improvement program replicable across the Wockhardt network</li>
<li>Creation of a nursing leadership development certification program for nurse managers from various Wockhardt hospitals</li>
<li>Review of existing and proposed clinical services and programs by expert faculty and hospital leaders from the top Harvard Medical School-affiliated hospitals</li>
<li>Numerous customized professional development programs for Wockhardt clinical and executive staff</li>
</ul>
<h3>Our Impact</h3>
<ul>
<li>Increased visibility of Wockhardt as a regional leader and major international health care destination, including international news coverage</li>
<li>Creation of a “culture of quality” that is part of the Wockhardt fabric and replicable across the network</li>
<li>Joint Commission International accreditation for two major Wockhardt hospitals</li>
<li>National recognition and respect for the Wockhardt nursing service</li>
<li>Outcomes of quality improvement initiatives have been highlighted at major health care industry conferences and publications (Example: decrease of hospital acquired infections through the accreditation preparation process)</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/case-studies/wockhardt-hospitals-limited">Wockhardt Hospitals Limited</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/?p=2372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOSTON, May 14, 2015 &#8212; In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners Medical International (PMI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. &#8220;Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and their ability&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015">PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>BOSTON, May 14, 2015</strong> &#8212; In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners Medical International (PMI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. &#8220;Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and their ability to lead, influence and impact improvements cannot be underestimated,&#8221; said Elizabeth Brown, Director of Nursing and Global Programs for PMI. This year&#8217;s theme for International Nurses Day is Nurses: A Force for Change: Care Effective, Cost Effective and PMI is kicking off activities by launching a digital library that will highlight global partnerships, projects and initiatives driven by the nurses from Partners HealthCare member hospitals including Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital, Massachusetts General Hospital, and the network&#8217;s affiliated community hospitals and departments.</p>
<p>According to the International Council of Nurses (ICN), sponsors of International Nurses Day, &#8220;nurses are part of the solution to achieve better health for all in a care effective, cost effective way.&#8221; The World Health Organization (WHO) reports the average number of nurses per population is estimated to be 29 for every 10,000 people, yet this rate differs drastically across countries and regions, challenging the safe, effective delivery of patient care. Lower nurse staffing, increased workloads, and unstable nursing unit environments are linked to negative patient outcomes ranging from falls to medication errors. As a result, nurses from the bedside to the boardroom are working to make a positive impact to improve how nurses are educated and how care is delivered.</p>
<p>As part of the year-long initiative, Partners is demonstrating how nurses across the world are embracing this year&#8217;s theme &#8220;Nurses globally are working to strengthen competencies as health care delivery becomes more complex, are being recognized as a valued member of the care team, and are dedicated to improving working conditions and the quality of care and patient safety,&#8221; said Brown.</p>
<p>For nearly 20 years PMI has had the opportunity to partner with global health care organizations for bilateral sharing of best practices to improve the critical skills of their nurses with the goal of providing safe, high-quality patient care. In its work with global partners, PMI engages the vast expertise and knowledge available throughout the Partners network. &#8220;We invite the global nursing community to visit our digital library throughout the year to learn how nurses are working to help innovate and shape the future of nursing worldwide,&#8221; said Brown.</p>
<p><strong>About Partners Medical International</strong><br />
Partners Medical International (PMI) a 503c not-for-profit corporation located in Boston, Massachusetts, USA. Its collaborative partners benefit from working relationships with clinical institutions within the Partners HealthCare System, one of the largest academic medical systems in the United States. Partners founding member hospitals, Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, are among the world&#8217;s most renowned medical institutions. To learn more about PMI, visit <a href="http://www.partners.org/partners-medical-international/Default.aspx">www.partnersmedicalinternational.org</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015">PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/?p=2371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This June, longstanding PMI partner New Age Wockhardt Hospital hosted the first annual symposium on “Sustaining Quality in Healthcare,” which drew healthcare quality experts, CEOs, chief nursing and medical officers and administrators from several multispecialty hospitals across Mumbai. Four PMI faculty participated in the forum, including John Helfrick, MD; Betsy Brown, RN, MSN, MBA, Joanne&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum">Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This June, longstanding PMI partner New Age Wockhardt Hospital hosted the first annual symposium on “Sustaining Quality in Healthcare,” which drew healthcare quality experts, CEOs, chief nursing and medical officers and administrators from several multispecialty hospitals across Mumbai.</p>
<p>Four PMI faculty participated in the forum, including John Helfrick, MD; Betsy Brown, RN, MSN, MBA, Joanne Ayoub and Patricia Folcarelli, RN, PhD. Local speakers included Dr K K Kalra, CEO of National Accreditation Board for Hospitals &#038; Healthcare Providers (NABH); Dr. GirdharGyani, Director General of Association of Healthcare Providers (AHPI); and Suresh Lulla, Founder &#038; MD of Qimpro Consultant.</p>
<p>The symposium was part of the launch of the Mumbai Healthcare Forum, an initiative “to engage healthcare professionals in quality healthcare, innovative healthcare practices and a robust hospital-to-hospital learning network,” as noted by Dr. Parag Rindani, Associate Vice President and Head of the New Age Wockhardt Hospitals, South Mumbai. Wockhardt plans for the Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum to drive additional activities in the coming months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum">Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
