<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Leadership &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="/staff-category/leadership/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 17:47:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Leadership &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mehul Mehta, MD</title>
		<link>/staff/mehul-mehta</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 20:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/staff/betsy-brown-copy-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As part of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s executive leadership group, Mehul Mehta, MD, provides strategic leadership and direction for PHI’s operations and programs. Over the last 14 years, Dr. Mehta has worked on multiple projects within both the private and public sectors in more than a dozen countries. These projects have focused on the development&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/staff/mehul-mehta">Mehul Mehta, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As part of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s executive leadership group, Mehul Mehta, MD, provides strategic leadership and direction for PHI’s operations and programs. Over the last 14 years, Dr. Mehta has worked on multiple projects within both the private and public sectors in more than a dozen countries. These projects have focused on the development of networked health care systems, integrated healthcare and medical education environments, research programs, governance structures, patient-related programs, and collaborative academic efforts. For each of these projects, he has provided strategic inputs and support at the key stages of project development, implementation operations, and growth.</p>
<p>Dr. Mehta is also actively involved with the operations and leadership of PHI including working with PHI’s key stakeholders at Partners HealthCare Systems and its clinical and academic institutions. Independently, Dr. Mehta participates on the advisory boards of a number of international non-profit institutions in a pro bono capacity.</p>
<p>Prior to joining PHI and its predecessor organizations, Dr. Mehta served as a consultant with McKinsey &amp; Company in their health care industry practice. Dr. Mehta received his MMBS and MS in Ophthalmology from the University of Bombay with distinction and honors. He completed his postgraduate clinical training in retinal diseases at the Massachusetts Eye and Ear Infirmary and Schepens Eye Research Institute of Harvard Medical School. He also holds a master’s degree in cognitive and neural systems from Boston University and has published, lectured and mentored students in the fields of globalization, global health care, and education systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/staff/mehul-mehta">Mehul Mehta, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>H. Thomas Aretz, MD</title>
		<link>/staff/thomas-aretz</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 20:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/staff/betsy-brown-copy</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>H. Thomas Aretz, MD, is a member of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s senior management team focusing largely on academic programs and institutions, such as universities, medical schools and academic medical centers. A native of Germany, Dr. Aretz has been in the academic practice of cardiovascular pathology since 1981. He was the course director of a&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/staff/thomas-aretz">H. Thomas Aretz, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>H. Thomas Aretz, MD, is a member of Partners HealthCare International (PHI)’s senior management team focusing largely on academic programs and institutions, such as universities, medical schools and academic medical centers.</p>
<p>A native of Germany, Dr. Aretz has been in the academic practice of cardiovascular pathology since 1981. He was the course director of a major integrated medical school course at Harvard from 1992 to 2005. He is a Program Director for the Harvard Macy Institute, and has been involved in international programs since 1996. He holds a clinical appointment at the Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH), where he completed his post-doctoral training. He has served on many academic and hospital (IRB chairman) committees and industrial boards, and is the co-founder of three medical technology companies. He received his medical degree from Harvard Medical School and is certified in anatomic and clinical pathology by the American Board of Pathology.</p>
<p>Dr. Aretz has lectured and published extensively and has received multiple teaching awards at Harvard Medical School and MGH. He has also won recognition for his efforts to improve medical education around the world through intra-institutional collaborations. In 2006 he was named an “Ehrenbürger” (honorary citizen)of the Ludwig Maximilians University in Munich for his contributions to the long-standing then-PHMI-LMU alliance. In 2007, he was recognized with a MILES Award (Mentoring, Innovation, and Leadership in Educational Scholarship), given by the Yong Loo Lin School of Medicine at the National University of Singapore, for outstanding contributions to the advancement of global medical education and academic medicine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/staff/thomas-aretz">H. Thomas Aretz, MD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
