<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Commercialization Council &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-type/commercialization-council/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 13:08:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Commercialization Council &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Susan Slaugenhaupt</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/susan-slaugenhaupt</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/susan-slaugenhaupt</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Susan is the inaugural Scientific Director of the newly formed MGH Research Institute, a strategic initiative that will support the entire research enterprise at MGH to foster and sustain medical innovation. Dr. Slaugenhaupt&#8217;s research focuses on two neurological disorders, familial dysautonomia (FD) and mucolipidosis type IV (MLIV), as well as the common cardiac disorder mitral&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/susan-slaugenhaupt">Susan Slaugenhaupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Susan is the inaugural Scientific Director of the newly formed MGH Research Institute, a strategic initiative that will support the entire research enterprise at MGH to foster and sustain medical innovation. Dr. Slaugenhaupt&#8217;s research focuses on two neurological disorders, familial dysautonomia (FD) and mucolipidosis type IV (MLIV), as well as the common cardiac disorder mitral valve prolapse (MVP). Discoveries in Dr. Slaugenhaupt’s laboratory have led to the successful implementation of critical population screening for FD and MLIV, and to the development of a treatment for FD that directly targets the mRNA splicing mechanism. This exciting work has led to a clinical trial of the first therapeutic for FD aimed at altering the molecular defect. In addition to her extensive groundbreaking research, Dr. Slaugenhaupt is a professor in the Department of Neurology at Massachusetts General Hospital and Harvard Medical School and a founding faculty member in the Center for Human Genetic Research. Dr. Slaugenhaupt spearheads several programs and educational initiatives at MGH, including a thriving undergraduate summer internship program. She also co-directs the Partners Biobank at MGH, an exciting initiative that will speed the translation of research discoveries into improved clinical care for MGH patients.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/susan-slaugenhaupt">Susan Slaugenhaupt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rudolph Tanzi</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/rudolph-tanzi</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/rudolph-tanzi</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rudolph Tanzi, PhD is the Director of the Genetics and Aging Research Unit and Vice-Chair of Neurology at Massachusetts General Hospital. He is also serves as the Joseph P. and Rose F. Kennedy Professor of Neurology at Harvard Medical School. Dr. Tanzi co-discovered three of the four known Alzheimer’s disease genes and directs the Alzheimer’s&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/rudolph-tanzi">Rudolph Tanzi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rudolph Tanzi, PhD is the Director of the Genetics and Aging Research Unit and Vice-Chair of Neurology at Massachusetts General Hospital. He is also serves as the Joseph P. and Rose F. Kennedy Professor of Neurology at Harvard Medical School. Dr. Tanzi co-discovered three of the four known Alzheimer’s disease genes and directs the Alzheimer’s Genome Project, which has identified several other Alzheimer’s genes. He also discovered the Wilson’s disease gene and participated in the discovery of several other neurological disease genes. He is co-founder of several biotech companies, including Prana Biotechnology, which has the Alzheimer’s drug, PBT2, in clinical trials. Dr. Tanzi has published over 450 papers and has received several awards, including the Metropolitan Life Foundation Award, Potamkin Prize, and one of the Top 100 Most Influential Harvard Alumni. He also co-authored the popular trade books “Decoding Darkness” and the New York Times Bestseller, “Super Brain” and occasionally plays keyboards for the band Aerosmith.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/rudolph-tanzi">Rudolph Tanzi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guillermo Tearney</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/guillermo-tearney</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/guillermo-tearney</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Guillermo Tearney, MD, PhD, is a professor of pathology at Harvard Medical School, an affiliated faculty member of the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology (HST) and the Mike and Sue Hazard Family Research Scholar at Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH). Dr. Tearney received his medical degree magna cum laude from Harvard Medical School and&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/guillermo-tearney">Guillermo Tearney</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Guillermo Tearney, MD, PhD, is a professor of pathology at Harvard Medical School, an affiliated faculty member of the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology (HST) and the Mike and Sue Hazard Family Research Scholar at Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH). Dr. Tearney received his medical degree magna cum laude from Harvard Medical School and holds a doctoral degree in electrical engineering and computer science from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.</p>
<p>The Tearney laboratory at the Wellman Center for Photomedicine focuses on the development and clinical validation of non-invasive, high-resolution optical imaging methods for disease diagnosis. Dr. Tearney&#8217;s lab was the first to perform human imaging in the coronary arteries and gastrointestinal tract in vivo with optical coherence tomography (OCT), which provides cross-sectional images of tissue architectural microstructure at a resolution of 10 μm. Dr. Tearney has also conducted many of the seminal studies validating OCT and is considered an expert on OCT image interpretation. Recently, Dr. Tearney&#8217;s lab has invented a next generation OCT technology, termed μOCT, which has a resolution of 1 μm and is capable of imaging cells and subcellular structures in the coronary wall. Dr. Tearney has also developed several other technologies, including a confocal endomicroscope capable of imaging the entire esophagus, an ultraminiature three-dimensional endoscope, a highly efficient form of near field scanning optical microscopy (NSOM), and novel fluorescence spectroscopy and multimodality imaging techniques. He has an active program in Raman spectroscopy and has conducted the first intracoronary Raman in vivo.</p>
<p>Dr. Tearney is co-editor of The Handbook of Optical Coherence Tomography and has published more than 170 peer-reviewed articles, including many that have been highlighted on the covers of <em>Science, Nature Medicine, Circulation, Gastroenterology</em>, and the <em>Journal of American College of Cardiology</em>.</p>
<p>Dr. Tearney’s work extends beyond his laboratory at MGH, many of his technologies are being produced commercially. He founded the <a href="http://www.octstandardization.org/site/">International Working Group on Intracoronary OCT Standardization and Validation</a>, a group dedicated to establishing standards to ensure the widespread adoption of this imaging technology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/guillermo-tearney">Guillermo Tearney</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ravi Thadhani</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ravi-thadhani</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/ravi-thadhani</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ravi Thadhani, MD, is a professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School and Chief of the Division of Nephrology at the Massachusetts General Hospital. He received his BS degree summa cum laude from The University of Notre Dame, his MD from the University of Pennsylvania, and his MPH from The Harvard School of Public Health.&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ravi-thadhani">Ravi Thadhani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ravi Thadhani, MD, is a professor of medicine at Harvard Medical School and Chief of the Division of Nephrology at the Massachusetts General Hospital. He received his BS degree summa cum laude from The University of Notre Dame, his MD from the University of Pennsylvania, and his MPH from The Harvard School of Public Health.</p>
<p>Dr. Thadhani is a clinical and translational investigator with a 15-year history of funding from the National Institutes of Health (NIH). He has performed several proof-of-concept studies, observational studies, and clinical trials, both with the NIH and industry. He has experience in developing diagnostic tests, some of which are used in the clinic today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ravi-thadhani">Ravi Thadhani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mehmet Toner</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/mehmet-toner</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/mehmet-toner</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mehmet Toner, PhD, is a professor of surgery at the Harvard Medical School, a professor of biomedical engineering at the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology (HST), Associate Director of the Center for Engineering in Medicine (CEM) at the Massachusetts General Hospital and Shriners Hospital for Children, and Director of the CEM-affiliated BioMEMS Resource&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/mehmet-toner">Mehmet Toner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mehmet Toner, PhD, is a professor of surgery at the Harvard Medical School, a professor of biomedical engineering at the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology (HST), Associate Director of the Center for Engineering in Medicine (CEM) at the Massachusetts General Hospital and Shriners Hospital for Children, and Director of the CEM-affiliated BioMEMS Resource Center. He holds an undergraduate degree in mechanical engineering from the Istanbul Technical University, and graduate degrees in mechanical and medical engineering from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT). Toner worked on his doctorate under the guidance of MIT professor Ernest Cravalho, one of the first engineering scientists to work on cryobiology.</p>
<p>Dr. Toner first gained prominence for his theory of intra-cellular ice formation while still in graduate school. Since then, he has made contributions to the specific fields of cryobiology and biopreservation, and to the wider field of biomedical engineering in the form of inventions, books, and journal publications. Dr. Toner&#8217;s early work focused on understanding cellular injuries during cryopreservation and finding optimum strategies for cell preservation. His later works include microfluidics, Bio-sensing and dry preservation of mammalian cells. Dr. Toner’s laboratories have produced several researchers and he continues to train post-doctoral fellows and graduate students from MIT and Harvard University.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/mehmet-toner">Mehmet Toner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jeff Karp</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jeff-karp</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/jeff-karp</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chemical Engineer Dr. Jeff Karp is a world leader in the fields of drug delivery, stem cell therapeutics, and tissue adhesives. He is an Associate Professor at Brigham and Women’s Hospital, Harvard Medical School, Principal Faculty at the Harvard Stem Cell Institute, and an affiliate faculty at the Broad Institute and at the Harvard-MIT Division&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jeff-karp">Jeff Karp</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chemical Engineer Dr. Jeff Karp is a world leader in the fields of drug delivery, stem cell therapeutics, and tissue adhesives. He is an Associate Professor at Brigham and Women’s Hospital, Harvard Medical School, Principal Faculty at the Harvard Stem Cell Institute, and an affiliate faculty at the Broad Institute and at the Harvard-MIT Division of Health Sciences and Technology.</p>
<p>He has published 100 peer-reviewed papers (with over 10,000 citations) and has given 210 national and international invited lectures and has 65 issued or pending patents. Several technologies developed in his lab have formed the foundation for multiple products on the market and currently under development and for the launch of four companies including <a href="http://www.geckobiomedical.com/">Gecko Biomedical</a><u>,</u> <a href="https://www.skintifique.me/en/">Skintifique</a>,<a href="http://www.frequencytx.com/">Frequency Therapeutics</a>, and <a href="http://www.aliviotherapeutics.com/">Alivio Therapeutics</a>.</p>
<p>The <em>Boston Business Journal</em> recognized him as a Champion in Healthcare Innovation and MIT’s <em>Technology Review Magazine </em>(TR35) also recognized Dr. Karp as being one of the top innovators in the world (3 members from his laboratory have received this award).</p>
<p>His work has been selected by <em>Popular Mechanic&#8217;s</em> &#8220;Top 20 New Biotech Breakthroughs that Will Change Medicine.” He gave a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AshPR7OsZA0">TEDMED talk</a> on bioinspired medical innovation and is a member of the TEDMED Editorial Advisory Board. In 2015 he received a Breakthrough Award from the Kenneth Rainin Foundation and was a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NR2jH3x6ahw">commencement speaker</a> at the University of Toronto.</p>
<p>Dr. Karp was selected as the Outstanding Faculty Undergraduate Mentor among all Faculty at MIT and he received the HST McMahon Mentoring award for being the top mentor of Harvard-MIT students. To date, 17 trainees from his laboratory have secured faculty positions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/jeff-karp">Jeff Karp</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ramin Khorasani</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ramin-khorasani</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/ramin-khorasani</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ramin Khorasani, MD, is the Vice Chair for Radiology at Brigham and Women’s Hospital (BWH); the Distinguished Chair for Medical Imaging IT at BWH; Director of the Quality, Safety and Information Technology programs for Medical Imaging; and Director of the Center for Evidence-Based Imaging at BWH. He received a medical degree from McGill University School&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ramin-khorasani">Ramin Khorasani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ramin Khorasani, MD, is the Vice Chair for Radiology at Brigham and Women’s Hospital (BWH); the Distinguished Chair for Medical Imaging IT at BWH; Director of the Quality, Safety and Information Technology programs for Medical Imaging; and Director of the Center for Evidence-Based Imaging at BWH. He received a medical degree from McGill University School of Medicine in Montreal, then completed an internship in internal medicine at Toronto General Hospital, University of Toronto. Following a diagnostic radiology residency, Dr. Khorasani completed an abdominal imaging and interventional fellowship at BWH and Harvard Medical School.</p>
<p>Dr. Khorasani’s research focuses on improving the quality and efficiency of care delivery using innovative technology solutions, including knowledge delivery in real time and at the point of care to reduce medical errors, costs and to improve the quality of care for both patients and providers. He has worked with computerized physician order entry (CPOE) systems and imaging CDS for 20 years, with extensive experience in developing, testing, implementing and evaluating imaging CDS integrated with an enterprise imaging CPOE system. Dr. Khorasani serves on several national/international non-profit organizations in healthcare imaging with focus on quality, safety and/or IT and has authored numerous peer-reviewed publications.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/ramin-khorasani">Ramin Khorasani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adam Landman</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adam-landman</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/adam-landman</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Adam Landman, MD, is an emergency physician and Chief Medical Information Officer for Health Information Innovation and Integration at the Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital (BWH). Dr. Landman holds degrees in information systems and health care policy from Carnegie Mellon University and a medical degree from UMDNJ &#8211; Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. After medical school,&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adam-landman">Adam Landman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adam Landman, MD, is an emergency physician and Chief Medical Information Officer for Health Information Innovation and Integration at the Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital (BWH). Dr. Landman holds degrees in information systems and health care policy from Carnegie Mellon University and a medical degree from UMDNJ &#8211; Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. After medical school, he trained in emergency medicine at the University of California, Los Angeles, and completed the RWJ Foundation Clinical Scholars fellowship in health services research, where he worked on qualitative and quantitative studies on the adoption of health information technology (HIT) in the emergency department (ED) and prehospital settings.</p>
<p>Dr. Landman focuses on the innovative use of information technology to improve health care delivery. He steered a three-year, $7 million, custom software development project to move BWH ED clinicians from paper-based to electronic documentation. He is currently responsible for clinical oversight of the implementation and integration of a new hospital laboratory system, as well as multiple projects related to a new enterprise EHR implementation, and health information innovation programs.</p>
<p>The Landman laboratory has received grant funding to build and pilot a mobile app for capturing and storing clinical images; use high-fidelity medical simulation centers to evaluate HIT in a controlled, safe environment; and build an improved electronic medication administration and reconciliation (e-MAR) system. Dr. Landman welcomes the opportunity to work with students and residents interested in clinical and research informatics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/adam-landman">Adam Landman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calum MacRae</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/calum-macrae</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/calum-macrae</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Calum MacRae is a cardiologist, geneticist and developmental biologist who trained in Edinburgh, London and Boston. He is Chief of Cardiovascular Medicine at Brigham and Women’s Hospital and Associate Professor of Medicine at Harvard Medical School. He is also an Associate Member at the Broad Institute and a Principal Faculty Member at the Harvard Stem&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/calum-macrae">Calum MacRae</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Calum MacRae is a cardiologist, geneticist and developmental biologist who trained in Edinburgh, London and Boston. He is Chief of Cardiovascular Medicine at Brigham and Women’s Hospital and Associate Professor of Medicine at Harvard Medical School. He is also an Associate Member at the Broad Institute and a Principal Faculty Member at the Harvard Stem Cell Institute. His research is focused on understanding the fundamental mechanisms of disease using human studies and complementary efforts combining systems level modeling with empiric high-throughput biology in the zebrafish. His lab uses automated screens in fish to define the genetic architecture of disease and to explore gene-drug (or environment) interactions through the interrogation of large-scale chemical libraries. His clinical interests include general cardiology, genomic medicine, innovation in phenotyping and the redesign of clinical care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/calum-macrae">Calum MacRae</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orhun Muratoglu</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/orhun-muratoglu</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ts_admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnershc.wpengine.com/council-member/orhun-muratoglu</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Orhun Muratoglu, PhD, is an associate professor at Harvard Medical School, the Alan Gerry Scholar at Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH), and Co-Director of the Harris Orthopaedics Lab (HOL) at MGH, and Director of the Technology Implementation and Research Center at MGH. Dr. Muratoglu holds a doctoral degree from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. The Muratoglu&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/orhun-muratoglu">Orhun Muratoglu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Orhun Muratoglu, PhD, is an associate professor at Harvard Medical School, the Alan Gerry Scholar at Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH), and Co-Director of the Harris Orthopaedics Lab (HOL) at MGH, and Director of the Technology Implementation and Research Center at MGH. Dr. Muratoglu holds a doctoral degree from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.</p>
<p>The Muratoglu laboratory explores the failure mechanisms of ultra high molecular weight polyethylene (UHMWPE) and attempts to develop technologies to address these failure modes. Dr. Muratoglu played a key role in the discovery of highly crosslinked UHMWPE, a more wear-resistant polymeric material for load-bearing applications in total joints. Implants manufactured using this technology have been placed in more than 3 million patients to date, with outstanding outcomes observed during the first decade of use. He also pioneered the use of the antioxidant vitamin E to further stabilize the highly cross-linked UHMWPE. Dr. Muratoglu also develops treatment modalities for early-stage osteoarthritis, in the form of cartilage repair and/or replacement by leveraging hydrogel technologies. He has published nearly 80 peer-reviewed articles, 30 book chapters, and holds more than 50 patents.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/council-member/orhun-muratoglu">Orhun Muratoglu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
