<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>General News &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/category/news/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:41:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>General News &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/?p=2371</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This June, longstanding PMI partner New Age Wockhardt Hospital hosted the first annual symposium on “Sustaining Quality in Healthcare,” which drew healthcare quality experts, CEOs, chief nursing and medical officers and administrators from several multispecialty hospitals across Mumbai. Four PMI faculty participated in the forum, including John Helfrick, MD; Betsy Brown, RN, MSN, MBA, Joanne&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum">Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This June, longstanding PMI partner New Age Wockhardt Hospital hosted the first annual symposium on “Sustaining Quality in Healthcare,” which drew healthcare quality experts, CEOs, chief nursing and medical officers and administrators from several multispecialty hospitals across Mumbai.</p>
<p>Four PMI faculty participated in the forum, including John Helfrick, MD; Betsy Brown, RN, MSN, MBA, Joanne Ayoub and Patricia Folcarelli, RN, PhD. Local speakers included Dr K K Kalra, CEO of National Accreditation Board for Hospitals &#038; Healthcare Providers (NABH); Dr. GirdharGyani, Director General of Association of Healthcare Providers (AHPI); and Suresh Lulla, Founder &#038; MD of Qimpro Consultant.</p>
<p>The symposium was part of the launch of the Mumbai Healthcare Forum, an initiative “to engage healthcare professionals in quality healthcare, innovative healthcare practices and a robust hospital-to-hospital learning network,” as noted by Dr. Parag Rindani, Associate Vice President and Head of the New Age Wockhardt Hospitals, South Mumbai. Wockhardt plans for the Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum to drive additional activities in the coming months.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/news/wockhardt-hospital-launches-first-annual-mumbai-healthcare-quality-forum">Wockhardt Hospital Launches First Annual Mumbai Healthcare Quality Forum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
