<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Press Releases &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<atom:link href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/category/press-releases/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:44:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/cropped-p-favicon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Press Releases &#8211; Partners Medical International</title>
	<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</title>
		<link>https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[muellerdesign]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 15:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Releases]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://partnersmed.wpengine.com/?p=2372</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOSTON, May 14, 2015 &#8212; In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners Medical International (PMI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. &#8220;Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and their ability&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015">PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>BOSTON, May 14, 2015</strong> &#8212; In recognition of International Nurses Day, Partners Medical International (PMI) this week announced a year-long global initiative that will focus on nurses as a force for change in improving health care quality, efficiency, education, and work environment. &#8220;Nurses represent the largest percent of our global healthcare workforce and their ability to lead, influence and impact improvements cannot be underestimated,&#8221; said Elizabeth Brown, Director of Nursing and Global Programs for PMI. This year&#8217;s theme for International Nurses Day is Nurses: A Force for Change: Care Effective, Cost Effective and PMI is kicking off activities by launching a digital library that will highlight global partnerships, projects and initiatives driven by the nurses from Partners HealthCare member hospitals including Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital, Massachusetts General Hospital, and the network&#8217;s affiliated community hospitals and departments.</p>
<p>According to the International Council of Nurses (ICN), sponsors of International Nurses Day, &#8220;nurses are part of the solution to achieve better health for all in a care effective, cost effective way.&#8221; The World Health Organization (WHO) reports the average number of nurses per population is estimated to be 29 for every 10,000 people, yet this rate differs drastically across countries and regions, challenging the safe, effective delivery of patient care. Lower nurse staffing, increased workloads, and unstable nursing unit environments are linked to negative patient outcomes ranging from falls to medication errors. As a result, nurses from the bedside to the boardroom are working to make a positive impact to improve how nurses are educated and how care is delivered.</p>
<p>As part of the year-long initiative, Partners is demonstrating how nurses across the world are embracing this year&#8217;s theme &#8220;Nurses globally are working to strengthen competencies as health care delivery becomes more complex, are being recognized as a valued member of the care team, and are dedicated to improving working conditions and the quality of care and patient safety,&#8221; said Brown.</p>
<p>For nearly 20 years PMI has had the opportunity to partner with global health care organizations for bilateral sharing of best practices to improve the critical skills of their nurses with the goal of providing safe, high-quality patient care. In its work with global partners, PMI engages the vast expertise and knowledge available throughout the Partners network. &#8220;We invite the global nursing community to visit our digital library throughout the year to learn how nurses are working to help innovate and shape the future of nursing worldwide,&#8221; said Brown.</p>
<p><strong>About Partners Medical International</strong><br />
Partners Medical International (PMI) a 503c not-for-profit corporation located in Boston, Massachusetts, USA. Its collaborative partners benefit from working relationships with clinical institutions within the Partners HealthCare System, one of the largest academic medical systems in the United States. Partners founding member hospitals, Brigham and Women&#8217;s Hospital and Massachusetts General Hospital, are among the world&#8217;s most renowned medical institutions. To learn more about PMI, visit <a href="http://www.partners.org/partners-medical-international/Default.aspx">www.partnersmedicalinternational.org</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/press-releases/pmi-launches-year-long-global-initiative-support-international-nurses-day-2015">PMI Launches Year-long Global Initiative in Support of International Nurses Day 2015</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://davekuhar.github.io/partners-med-static/">Partners Medical International</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
